(Sheldon:)I trust you paid off
those parking tickets.
(Ms Jenson:)Yes, I did.
(Sheldon:)Hearing unimpaired. Good.
(Ms Jenson:)Look, Dr. Cooper,
I really want this position.
It would be an incredible honor
to work for a man of your brilliance.
(Sheldon:)Flattery will not get you this job,
Ms. Jensen.
(Ms Jenson:)It's not flattery if it's the truth.
(Howard:)Oh.
(Sheldon:)Well, thank you. Welcome aboard.
- Talked to Howard, lately?
- Yeah, last night.
(Raj:)He kept making me drop pencils
for him.
(Raj:)I got uncomfortable.
(Raj:)Hope you're hungry.
They're serving macaroni and...
...cheese.
(Leonard:)Smooth.
(Penny:)- Hi.
- Hello.
Aren't you gonna introduce us?
(Sheldon:)No. I have people for that now.
You're up.
(Ms Jenson:)I'm Alex, Dr. Cooper's new assistant.
(Leonard:)Ah, congratulations,
and may God have mercy on your soul.